newmajority.com 2009-09-11

# Privacy Policy

Welcome to [www.newmajority.com](http://www.newmajority.com/) operated by New Majority LLC (”NewMajority.com”, “We”, “Us” or “Our”). This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use, and retain personally identifiable information you provide to us through our website, and to assist you in making informed decisions when using the website. At NewMajority.com we appreciate your readership and value your personal privacy. We respect the personal nature of the information you provide us on our website and acknowledge the importance of protecting this information. This policy may be revised or updated at any time and we encourage you to check back often to ensure that you are familiar with the most recent version and the terms of our policy.

**When does NewMajority.com collect my personal information?**  
The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected by NewMajority.com include: name, e-mail address, city, and state. You may provide such personal information to NewMajority.com (1) by sharing your e-mail address and subscribing to email newsletters, forums or requesting site updates, or (2) by sharing personal information when you post comments on our posts or stories. NewMajority.com may also ask for other information at other times but at no time will you be required to share any personal information to gain complete access to our site. In addition to personal information—such as name, e-mail addresses, city, and state—NewMajority.com may also collect information that is in no way personally identifiable. This may include the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Microsoft Windows or Mac OS), the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink), and the websites you visit directly before and after your visit to NewMajority.com.

**How does NewMajority.com use my personal information?**  
The more we know about you, the better we are able to customize our website to suit your personal preferences and interests. The e-mail address you provide may be used by NewMajority.com for any reason, such as contacting you for editorial purposes or to advise you of any changes to our site. We may also from time to time send you messages about our marketing partners’ products. The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services. If you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., a letter to our editors, a posting to a blog or a discussion board), we may publish your screen name and other information you have provided to us. We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services. To maintain a site that is free of charge and does not require registration, we display advertisements on our website. We also use the information you give us to help our advertisers target the audience they want to reach. At no time does any party other than NewMajority.com have access to the personally identifiable information you provide to us, and you will not be contacted by any party other than NewMajority.com. The only exceptions to the foregoing are that we may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our website and applicable laws or as otherwise required or permitted by law or consistent with legal requirements. In addition, we may transfer personally identifiable information about you if we are acquired by, sold to, or merged with another company. Although NewMajority.com takes commercially reasonable precautions to safeguard against loss, unauthorized access, and illegal use or disclosure of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Statement.

**Cookies**  
To enhance your experience with NewMajority.com, our web pages use “cookies.” Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site.

**Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites, Ad-Servers and Sponsors.**  
Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites, Ad-Servers and Sponsors. Some of our Web pages may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy notices as NewMajority.com has no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. NewMajority.com sometimes may offer content (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, or promotions) that is sponsored by or cobranded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. NewMajority.com has no control over these third parties’ use of this information. The site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such information. NewMajority.com may use a reputable third party to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at its Web pages. These third party ad servers may use cookies, web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements’ effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our privacy statement. We have also contracted with a number of advertising network partners to monitor certain pages of our website and RSS feeds for the purpose of reporting website and RSS traffic, statistics, advertisement ‘click-throughs’, and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, these advertising network partners may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to these network partners. Third parties and websites that have links on our site may also collect or use information about you. The information practices of other companies or people that NewMajority.com does not employ or manage are not covered by this privacy statement.

**How to Contact Us.**  
If you have any questions or concerns about the online privacy statement for this site or its implementation you may contact us at [privacy@newmajority.com](mailto:privacy@newmajority.com).

**Is there anything else I should know about my privacy and NewMajority.com?**  
This is a general use Website and is not geared to children. NewMajority.com does not knowingly collect, use or retain personally identifiable information from anyone who is under thirteen (13) years of age. We will delete any records of such personally identifiable information that come to our attention. If it comes to your attention that a child under thirteen (13) years of age has provided any personally identifiable information to NewMajority.com, we invite you to notify us at privacy@newmajority.com so that we may delete the information from our records. Any information you disclose voluntarily on our comments pages or in any forums we may develop in the future becomes public information. We cannot control the actions of our site users and advise you to use your discretion in sharing information about yourself on the Internet. All information sharing is optional and done so at your own risk. Privacy is a very personal matter and we encourage you to be careful and responsible when disclosing personal information online.
